It is flowing, sir.
Yes!
So the water is this.
The water is this.
That's great.
It's not Friday.
Okay, then.
Shall we go?
Yes, sir.
I'm sure you're all looking forward to it.
That's right.
Mayama has a meeting today.
She's not.
I'm so embarrassed.
You just made a really serious face.
It's like when you're at home and there's this detective who says he's not in the office because he's got a meeting today.
I'm sure there's a detective here today.
bgp the village will be on stage tomorrow and I want a yakiniku bento lunch box with an early lunch box....
I'm sure you've heard of me... but I'm not so sure.
I don't care what you call it, but I think it should be "live delivery.
I'm glad to hear you're all doing well.
I'm glad to see you all looking so well... and I'm glad to see you all looking so well.
I'm almost in a bad way... it's a Tokyo Love Story... a Tokyo Love Story... so I'm fine.
I don't know if you can feel it or not... but this is the best time of year for me.
But now that I can walk, even just walking normally, I'm overjoyed.
Don't shake your boo-boo back at me.
I'm going to be a pirate king! I'm walking like one! And the stairs...
I'm going to be a pirate king! I'm going to be a pirate king!
But it was fine.
Okira came to see the disc, but even then it was great!
Who are you imitating?
I'm suspicious today, but I'm acting suspiciously, so I'm nervous when I go to the venue...
ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah...
It's like you're in an all-girls' school.
It's always tense, isn't it?
Well then, let's get on with the recording.
Yes.
I wonder what it is...
It smells like a fragrant osmanthus.
It smells like a fragrance of Kinmokusei.
I love kinmoki-rhinoceros!
It's only a little time in a year, isn't it?
That's right, very little time, isn't it?
The fragrance of Kinmorinoki is indescribable.
What's that? It's like...
Yes.
Like "ah-ha".
It's that time of year again.
How are you feeling autumn?
Yes, I'm feeling it.
Because autumn is the time of year when I want to have birthdays and stuff.
I love autumn.
It's pretty exciting, isn't it?
There are birthdays in the fall, and it's a nice time of year.
And the food is delicious.
That's for sure.
From the end of October to the beginning of November.
It might be nice.
But early May is also good.
Early May.
Birthday parties and such.
It's easy to spend time there.
By the way, Savo... is it January?
January.
It's cold.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
It's cold and I don't feel like going outside in the morning.
No, no, no, no, no, it's New Year, it's New Year, it's New Year, it's festive
It's so cold
I can't get out of the house.
It's fine
Well, well, well, well, well, well...
That's how it is.
I'll get right to it.
We were just talking about Kinmokusai.
Kinmokusaisya.
Kinsha for short
Kinsha, Kinsha, Kinsha
This is also a very rare event that takes place only a few hours a year.
I'd like to introduce it to you.
Let's see...
Here we go.
Mr. No More Running is a man from Kanagawa Ward, Yokohama City, who works for a company.
He's an office worker at a company.
I'll do production, make copies, and hand them out to everyone in the holding room.
Then you hand them out to everyone.
What do you do with a computer?
On a computer, you know... in Excel, you know...
I make graphs. Graphs.
I passed last year and stood up. My shoulders were stiff.
You know that weird pillow thing?
Just go to the mail.
I can't run anymore, by the way.
Bite shrimp, Master Sarpon, Bill.
Well, the heat has completely disappeared and the mornings and evenings are getting much cooler.
When I was walking outside, I saw beautifully blooming golden osmanthus trees that signal the beginning of autumn, so I'll give you a picture of them.
So here it is, the golden rhinoceros!
How cute!
It's so cute, isn't it, with this orange color?
It was the top I discovered when I was looking for it, wondering where the fragrance was coming from.
That's right.
The fragrance of the golden osmanthus is not so noticeable when it's not in bloom.
Suddenly it's not in bloom.
Well, okay, but aren't plants amazing?
It's amazing, isn't it?
They follow the seasons.
They bloom and smell like this.
That's great!
But I got stung by crabs yesterday.
Crabs?
Kay...
KA
CA
C is for "C.
Kay.
I think there's still a "K.
I've got a goldeneye, too.
I've been stabbed by a Caye in about eight places.
Why? Why? Why?
My feet itch so bad.
Right and left.
It's itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy.
I've got a bug here!
Stop it, you're ruining my dreams!
I'm putting it all over my feet!
Itchy, itchy, master itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy
Itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy
But I thought there weren't many golden osmanthus.
On the contrary.
Kay's probably been too hot to work lately.
Summer was so hot.
It's too hot to be active when it's over 30 degrees.
On the contrary...
Come to think of it, we haven't had a Summer.
I didn't have a summer once.
Usually in the evening, when I go to performances...
I always see Summer, but this year I don't see her.
By the way...
Here you go.
What's this?
He's in a hurry to tell us what he's gonna tell us.
What do you want to talk about?
I mean, there haven't been many cicadas this year.
Cicadas were scarce this year.
I like cicadas, so I'm always watching them.
What's the percentage of oil?
Percentage of ming-ming
TSUKUTSUKUHIRO
And I wonder how many cicadas there are.
I've hardly heard a cicada this year.
Really?
But there were a lot of cicadas.
Machida, you see, are more abundant in nature.
There were a lot of echidnas, too.
There were.
So there are some in that area, too?
That's right.
The Yokohama one went to Machida.
It's been a long time.
I'm a city guy, so I'm not going to ask.
A man in the city center.
Men in the city center don't listen to cicadas.
Men in the heart of the city don't listen to cicadas.
A man of the city...
I say "city man" because he's a regular guy.
A city man.
City boy... it's just... it's... it's... it's just... it's just...
No, no, there's also this...
What's so great about plants?
You know, when you have a lot of trees and stuff...
They get caught in power lines and stuff.
They get cut down a lot, don't they?
It's the same with street trees.
In my neighborhood...
There was a tree that was cut down like this.
As I recall, it was huge.
And you know...
From where it was cut down...
It's really growing.
It's growing like a tree.
Isn't it amazing?
It's totally like that.
It's like the cheerleaders do this. Like this.
Blah, blah, blah.
Isn't it great?
It hasn't even been standing that long since it was cut.
It sure is amazing.
In the blink of an eye, these sprouts, these new branches?
It's a little misshapen now that it's been cut.
It's like I don't like them.
For them, too.
It's like, "Oh, I can live with this.
He's tough.
You have to be strong.
You're a plant, aren't you?
Well, well, well... with all that going on...
Also, today is the first day of November!
There are so many anniversaries on the first day of November.
It's 111.
I wonder what it is.
I think there are a lot of anniversaries on January 11th, too.
First of all, it's Dog Day.
Doggie Day.
That's what you mean.
Dog Day
Interview
It's just "Wan Wan Wan"...
It's a day to learn about dogs and love dogs.
Do you have a dog?
Yes, I do.
What kind of dog?
I have a dachshund.
Dachshund.
Miniature Dachshund
Do you know?
Yes, I know.
Yes, I know the Miniature Dachshund.
Two things about them.
Like this.
Like what?
Height.
About this tall?
Isn't it miniature?
Like 1/144 scale.
I'd have to compare it to a Gunpla.
Long torso, short legs.
Like a dachshund dachshund dachshund.
Yes, it is.
Like this
Such a long one.
Such a long one
A little tiny version of a dachshund.
Dachshunds are only used for miniature dachshunds.
A miniature dachshund.
There is such a breed, isn't there?
I have a miniature dachshund.
She loves it.
He's adorable.
Does he doggy doo?
Yes, he does.
It's so loud.
What's it look like?
It's like...
I've never heard that before.
It's just a little dog that sounds like that.
Yes, they do.
A little high pitched.
My parents told me to stay home yesterday.
I stayed at home.
Wait a minute.
How old are you?
Twenty-five.
A 25-year-old dachshund.
You're home alone?
You're home alone.
You're his parents, too, right?
I mean, a 25-year-old man with a 25-year-old dog.
I mean, a 25-year-old man with a dog.
I can't leave the house for long periods of time without someone there.
It's not like I said, "Go home for a while.
That's right.
He asked me to stay at home.
"Maya, can you stay at home? I said...
I told Shingo I'd stay home that day.
"I'm going to be your housemate for the day, so don't put in any work for me.
I don't know what you mean.
Stay at home?
I don't know.
And you'll be with your dog the whole time.
His name is Tam.
Tam?
The drummer.
Tam.
I'm from Tam.
With Tam.
Tam-tam-tam.
Tum-tum-tum.
tam tam tam tam tam tam tam tam tam tam tam tam tam
Okay, well, the dog.
Well, I hope you're well.
He's fine, he's fine, he's fine.
He's very curious.
He's basically on the first floor.
But I'm usually upstairs.
When I take him upstairs...
When I take him upstairs, he looks for things.
Looking for something.
Like there might be something there.
It's so unusual.
That's right.
I couldn't stay with him upstairs.
That's why I stayed downstairs all the time.
Staying at home.
You did well.
Thank you very much.
You were a good housekeeper.
You're a good keeper.
Maybe your mom and dad would say thank you, too.
Today, I'm going to treat you to some ice cream.
Oh, I didn't drink.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not drinking this.
What are you talking about?
It's like a skinny diaper.
I wanted it, though.
Well, well, well...
Also, November 1st is the anniversary of the University of Tokyo.
The first year of the Meiji era.
November 1, 1868.
Kannonzaki Todai in Yokosuka, Kanagawa Prefecture
Japan's first Western-style Tokyo University was built.
I wonder if they built it or what.
It was the first one there.
Yes, it was.
That's amazing.
I've been to Kannonzaki Todai in Yokosuka.
It was right at the very beginning
It gets a little lonely
It gets a little lonely in the evening
There's no one around
You're early for that kind of thing in Yokohama.
It's pretty early, but it's supposed to be.
Yokosuka's a bit... you know...
That's why there's so many of them.
A lot of them came from overseas.
Like the Perry thing...
I see...
Perry things...
I'm sorry.
It's nice.
Well, well, well...
We're here to trade.
The Perrys.
The Perrys!
Perrys.
The Perrys are here.
From USA
Cool!
It's the most... I mean, it's the Tokyo version.
It was Edo's version back then.
It's like the best defense of the city.
Oh...
Well, I guess the University of Tokyo is the same.
The University of Tokyo is probably...
I guess they built it later when more and more boats started to pass through there.
Yes... it's an important place...
It's also the day of radio calisthenics.
November 1, 1928 the first radio calisthenics was broadcast at 7:00 a.m. Who was the choreographer of that?
I don't know...
By the way, there's also Radio Gymnastics No. 1 and No. 2.
I know the difference between the first and the second... some kind of concept.
First of all, the place of the body, yes, yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Armor is better, it's moving
It's like a can!
To this world, the first one is almost right, it's for children to the elderly, so it's easy to move, it's for adults to move
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a little bit of a "kunina" in there, but it's a great idea to have a little bit of a "kunina" in there as well.
geht
Two of them are the second one, the second one, the first one, right?
That's the one like this, right?
The second one, you know, the second one, the second one, the second one.
The second one...
There's like two cushions in there.
The second time, when I was in elementary school, the girls didn't like it.
It's a little bit embarrassing, this kind of pose.
It's a little embarrassing, you know.
It's like, "Hmmm, hmmm, hmmm.
You know the third idea?
Yes, the third idea.
It's very difficult.
That's why it didn't become popular.
It's too much, too much, too much...
It's a little complicated.
Why did you think you could do it?
You have to make a move, right?
That's right.
Unfortunately, it didn't catch on.
It was short-lived.
So it's over. And the third one, too.
It was designed to strengthen muscles.
Radio Gymnastics 3.
You mean like core exercises?
It's for strengthening, not flexibility.
Well, well, well, well...
So, there are many anniversaries.
There are many anniversaries.
November 1st.
Wow, that's pretty good.
I guess November 1, 2011 would have been good, too.
I'm sure it would have been nice.
Kip and all.
It would be "ta-da!
I'm sure January 11th would have been the same, but...
Well, well, well...
That's how it is.
Oh, the live broadcast will be ending soon.
But since we're here, let's see if we can't get to it.
Anybody else celebrating a birthday soon?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's too close.
When's your birthday, Yoshida-san?
November 2nd.
Next month already.
You're already 26 years old.
Twenty-six. Isn't that really Arasawa?
Wait! I said "arasawa" during this show, or when my sister had her birthday.
In case you don't make it 45, but 25 years old in the middle, it's still, no longer.
That's exactly what I mean by "arasawa", isn't it?
What should I do, what should I do, what should I do? What should I do?
What should I do?
What should I do? Let's calm down a little.
You've been saying that for a long time.
Since you were 24 or 3 years old.
So, it's time for the annual gift-giving!
Yay!
I don't think I'm getting a present for the first time today!
Well, in that case!
Oh, what?
Oh, my gosh!
What is that?
Oh, what is it? What?
It's something like this.
What?
What is this? Well, Ki...kiyoshi?
I can't read it.
Kinashi cycle?
Kinashi Cycle!
Bicycle?
Tunnel-san's.
Oh, you must have a lot of soccys, right?
Oh, I can't ride a bike, is that OK?
Heh, heh, heh.
Hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi.
Ah, Kinashi cycle for sure.
Devil's Charge.
Oh, wow!
Wow!
What's this?
What is it?
A headband?
Here, put it on.
Hat four hats!
Golf center!
Oh, no!
Yikes!
Oh, these are arm covers.
Wow! This way to avoid sunburn.
I see!
Wow! Thank you!
Wow!
How did I get here yesterday?
Yes.
Dolph went to the golf course?
I made my debut!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
How did it feel? How did it feel?
Did it feel good?
To be honest, my muscles are really sore.
That bad?
Oh, yeah.
It felt so good, and the weather was so nice.
I came back from overseas yesterday, so I had to take the day off.
That's why my friends were so eager to go.
I said I'll definitely go on my day off, but the weather was not so good, and the bunkers were very difficult.
It was very difficult to get the sand out of the bunker.
Even the pros have a hard time with that, but it was a lot of fun.
I was thinking of going back in the fall when it's cooler.
I was thinking of going again because it's cooler in the fall.
I want to grow up!
It's like a poker chip, you think to Brynn that this is my ball, and you put it in the front, and it goes here, and here comes someone else's ball, and you're like, "Oh my God, here comes someone else's ball.
I did that.
I did it.
I'm not a good golfer and I'm not a good caddie, but my friends are beginners, so my caddie is like a teacher.
The moment you putt the putter in... that moment in golf... what's this?
Boo-boo!
Poron!
Wait a minute... you do the sticks like this... and then you hit the ground like this... and then you hit it in this direction... and then you hit it in this direction.
I see... the teacher is a teacher...
We were your mother, too.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I'll use it a lot.
I'll use it a lot.
Kahiho, I want a demo! I want one!
Thank you Takmin Chee, you got one too
Thank you very much. I want the Alaska demo. I want it.
I'll be 60 years old and I'll still want one
Even if I'm 78.
I'm an adult and my golf car is awesome and my muscles ache so much and my mom is a great example of how I can help.
I'll use it a lot.
I'm sure you'll get better at it the more you do it.
Well, well, well...
Now then, may I call it a time for the demons to end?
I'll see you next week at 8:00 a.m.
September is the 99th month, not the 100th, is that right?
Thank you very much.
See you next week!